Guide to the Pittsburgh Playhouse School of the Theater Records, 1934-1994 CTC.1981.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Production and General Files, 1934-1974; I.
  - Playhouse Gallery - Miscellaneous exhibit lists (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Playhouse Gallery - Donations and Exhibit Lists (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Playhouse Planning Committee, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Playhouse Plus - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Playhouse Plus - Meeting Minutes (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Playhouse Plus - Meeting programs (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Oakland Study - Summary of Recommendations [Pittsburgh Regional Planning Association], [1951] (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Office space available (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Once Upon A Mattress - Notes and memos (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Opening Night List (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Parking Problems (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Parks Commission - Films, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Personnel contact sheets (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Physical Plant - Renovation invoices, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Pinkerton Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 9-12)
  - Pinter Plays - Notes and memos (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Pittsburgh Amusement Tax (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre - Petroucka, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Pittsburgh Playhouse Dilemma by Richard Hoover, November 1967 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Pittsburgh Playhouse School of the Theater Pilot Study of Food and Beverage Departments, January 1962 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Plan for Developing Long-Range Financial Support (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Plaza Suite - Notes and memos (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Pittsburgh National Bank Statement of Income receipts, March 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Point Park College - Administrative Memos, 1966-1968 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Point Park College - Invoices from Pittsburgh Playhouse, 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Point Park Players - Notes and memos (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Public reaction, 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Private Trade School License Bond, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Production Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Production Expenses, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Production Notes - General, 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 9-10)
  - Production Time Table for Stage Managers, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Projects to be completed (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Promotion Committee, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Prop Shop inventory, August 1970 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Prop Shop inventory, March 1972 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Public Service announcements (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Playhouse Plus - Membership (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Playhouse Plus - Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Playhouse Plus - Record of Volunteer Work (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Playhouse Poll, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Playhouse postcards (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Playhouse Press brochure (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Playhouse Press - Orders and notes (Box 31, Folder 4-5)
  - Playhouse Proposal - University of Pittsburgh, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Playhouse School - Applications (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Playhouse School - Brochures (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Playhouse School - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Playhouse School - Comparative balance sheets, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Playhouse School - Donations, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Playhouse School - Laboratory Attendance sheets (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Playhouse School - Licenses (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Playhouse School - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Playhouse School - Organizational Chart (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Playhouse School - Point Park College Student Lists (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Playhouse School - Reports (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Playhouse School - Student Information Sheets (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Playhouse School - Students and Actors' Equity, 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Playhouse School - Student Excuses, 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Playhouse School - Quarterly tax returns, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
  - Rashomon - Notes and memos (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate Tax Appeal, 1963-1966 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Refurbishment, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Refurbishment, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Rehearsal and performance - General guidelines, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Arms and the Man, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Born Yesterday, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Catch Me If You Can, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Cinderella, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Delicate Balance, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Everything in the Garden, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Galileo, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Ghost Sonata, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Guys and Dolls, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Gypsy, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Hay Fever, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Rehearsal Logs - The Hostage, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Jack and the Beanstalk, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Joe Egg, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Land of the Dragon, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Little Red Riding Hood, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Luv, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Man's a Man, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Mystery at Crooked Pine Ranch, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Odd Couple, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Owl and the Pussy Cat, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Rashomon, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Room Service, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Rehearsal Logs - The Serpent, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Star Spangled Girl, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Subject Was Roses, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Rehearsal Logs - Three Men, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Renovation Committee notes, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Renovation paint colors (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Renovation - Proposal, construction bids, and notes, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Rentals - Auditoriums, 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 19-20)
  - Restaurant - Banquet Prospectus forms, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Restaurant - Banquet Prospectus forms, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 1-5)
  - Restaurant - Budget for renovations, August 1967 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Restaurant - Finances related correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Restaurant - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 3-4)
  - Restaurant - Correspondence with National Food, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Restaurant - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
  - Restaurant - Correspondence w/ Customers, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Restaurant - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Restaurant - Correspondence w/ Point Park College, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Restaurant - Menus (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Restaurant - Payroll Lists, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Restaurant - Placement Service Recommendations, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Restaurant - Summary Record of income, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Restaurant - Supply price lists, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Restaurant - Title transfer, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Project [American Conservatory Theatre] (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Proposal - Playwrights, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Role of the Total Playhouse Complex in the Pittsburgh Community, [1968?] (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Room Service - Notes and memos (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Royalties (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Running Crew Assignments, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Safety Deposit Box contents (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Scheduling, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Show Biz Spotlite [WVCT-TV], November 16, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Shuttle Schedule, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Specifications of Labor and Material for Additions and Alterations to Stage Facilities at the Pittsburgh Playhouse, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Spence, Sharon (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Spring Break Schedules, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Stagecraft Labs (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Adaptation (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Anything Goes (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Arms and the Man, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Born Yesterday, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Blithe Spirit, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Boys in the Band, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Cactus Flower, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Carousel (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Catch Me If You Can, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Cinderella, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Cindy, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Coppelia - Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Dear Me, The Sky is Falling, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Delicate Balance, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Do Your Own Thing, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Enter a Free Man, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Everything in the Garden, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Fiddler on the Roof, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - 40 Carats, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Galileo, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Ghost Sonata, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Goldilocks and the Three Bears (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Guys and Dolls, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Gypsy, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Hay Fever, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Henry IV, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - The Hostage, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - How the Other Half Loves, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Irma La Douce, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Jack and the Beanstalk, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Land of the Dragon, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Last of the Red Hot Lovers, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Lion in Winter, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Little Foxes, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Little Red Riding Hood, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Loot, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Luv, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Magic Horn, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Man of La Mancha, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Mystery of Crooked Pine Ranch, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Mystery at the Old Fort, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Never Too Late, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - No Strings, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Odd Couple, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Owl and the Pussycat, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Playhouse Jr. Ballet, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Plaza Suite, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Prime of Miss Jean Brodie, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Rapunzel (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Rashomon, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Red Juice, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Room Service, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Salvation, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Shoemaker, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - The Serpent, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Sing to Me, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Star Spangled Girl, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Streetcar Named Desire, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Streets of New York, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Subject Was Roses, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Three Men, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Three One-Acts, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Stage Manager's Reports - You Can't Take It With You, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Streetcar Named Desire - Notes and memos (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Streets of New York - Oleo File (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Student identification cards, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Student locker assignments, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Student resumes, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Study of Feasibility of Formal Association of The Pittsburgh Playhouse School of the Theater and Carnegie Institute of Technology Drama Department (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Subject Was Roses - Notes and memos (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Subscription/Sales Committee, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Subscription/Membership, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Suppliers (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Survey, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Survival Plan for the Pittsburgh Playhouse, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Tax Return - Federal, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Teacher's monthly payroll - Part-time, 1957-1958 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Three Rivers Arts Festival, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Three Rivers Arts Festival - Recommendations, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Three Sisters - Notes and memos (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Tickets - Miscellaneous unused (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Ticket price change (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Traffic tickets (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Two for the Seesaw - Notes and memos (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Union (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Upstage - Playhouse Guild Newsletter, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Vanguard Theatre - Proposal, [1963-1964?] (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Volkswagen bus - Title and registration (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Water survey, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Weekly reports, 1970-1973 (Box 41, Folder 1-4)
  - As You Like It - Poster (Oversize 42, Folder 1)
  - Evening of 3 One-Act Plays - Poster (Oversize 42, Folder 2)
  - Graphic Layouts - Miscellaneous (Oversize 42, Folder 3-5)
  - The Lady's Not for Burning - Poster (Oversize 42, Folder 6)
  - Once in a Lifetime - Expansion Proposal Brochure (Oversize 42, Folder 7)
  - Paul Sills' Story Theater (Oversize 42, Folder 8)
  - Point Park College Contemporary Theater - Poster, 1974 (Oversize 42, Folder 9)
  - Restaurant menus (Oversize 42, Folder 10)
  - Plan file (Map-case 1)
- Business and Financial Records, 1944-1973; II.
  These files, reports, and ledgers provide detailed financial data on the operation of the Playhouse complex including Bank Statements, Daily Box Office Reports, Employees' Wage Records, and Audit Reports.
  - Account numbers (Box 43A, Folder 1)
  - Accounts payable, 1966 (Box 43A, Folder 2)
  - G-Z, 1968-1969 (Box 43A, Folder 3-4)
  - Accounts payable, August 1971 (Box 43A, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report - Financial notes and figures (Box 43A, Folder 6)
  - Automatic Retailers of America (Box 43A, Folder 7)
  - Accounts payable - Current fund, 1969-1970 (Box 43B, Folder 1)
  - Accounts payable - Theater and restaurant, 1970-1972 (Box 43B, Folder 2-3)
  - Accounts payable - Incomplete, 1972-1973 (Box 43B, Folder 4)
  - Bank Statements - Mellon National Bank account #1, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Bank Statements - Mellon National Bank account #2, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Bank Statements - Mellon National Bank deferred income, 1967-1974 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Bank Statements - Mellon National Bank educational fund, 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Bank Statements - Mellon National Bank operating fund, 1967-1974 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Bank Statements - Mellon National Bank payroll account, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Bank Statements - Pittsburgh National Bank credit card charges, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Bank Statements - Union National Bank, 1971-1973 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Bank Statements - Western Pennsylvania National Bank, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Box Office discrepancy reports, 1971-1972 (Box 45A, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - After Hours, 1967 (Box 45A, Folder 2)
  - Box Office Reports - Aladdin, 1968 (Box 45A, Folder 3)
  - Box Office Reports - Amahl and the Night Visitors, 1971 (Box 45A, Folder 4)
  - Box Office Reports - Antigone, 1965 (Box 45A, Folder 5)
  - Box Office Reports - Anything Goes, 1971 (Box 45A, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Reports - April Fools, 1973 (Box 45A, Folder 7)
  - Box Office Reports - Ballet, 1969-1971 (Box 45A, Folder 8-10)
  - Box Office Reports - Ballet Jr., 1971 (Box 45A, Folder 11)
  - Box Office Reports - Ballet, 1972 (Box 45A, Folder 12)
  - Box Office Reports - Barefoot in the Park, 1967 (Box 45A, Folder 13)
  - Box Office Reports - Beyond the Fringe, 1965 (Box 45A, Folder 14)
  - Box Office Reports - Birthday Party, 1971 (Box 45A, Folder 15)
  - Box Office Reports - Black Musical, 1971 (Box 45A, Folder 16)
  - Box Office Reports - Blithe Spirit, 1971 (Box 45A, Folder 17)
  - Box Office Reports - Both Your Houses, 1946 (Box 45A, Folder 18)
  - Box Office Reports - Boy Meets Girl, 1946 (Box 45A, Folder 19)
  - Box Office Reports - Boys in the Band, 1972 (Box 45A, Folder 20)
  - Box Office Reports - Brave Little Tailor, 1972 (Box 45A, Folder 21)
  - Box Office Reports - Brockett and Barbara Upstairs, 1969 (Box 45A, Folder 22)
  - Box Office Reports - Cactus Flower, 1972 (Box 45A, Folder 23)
  - Box Office Reports - Caine Mutiny Court Martial, 1955 (Box 45B, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - Career, 1966 (Box 45B, Folder 2)
  - Box Office Reports - Carousel, 1973 (Box 45B, Folder 3)
  - Box Office Reports - Catch Me If You Can, 1971 (Box 45B, Folder 4)
  - Box Office Reports - Chastity, 1970 (Box 45B, Folder 5)
  - Box Office Reports - Christmas Nightingale, 1950 (Box 45B, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Reports - Cinderella, 1953 (Box 45B, Folder 7)
  - Box Office Reports - Cinderella, 1965 (Box 45B, Folder 8)
  - Box Office Reports - Cinderella, 1970 (Box 45B, Folder 9)
  - Box Office Reports - Cindy, 1970 (Box 45B, Folder 10)
  - Box Office Reports - Cold Turkey, 1971 (Box 45B, Folder 11)
  - Box Office Reports - Complaisant Lover, 1966 (Box 45B, Folder 12)
  - Box Office Reports - Crazy Cricket Farm, 1952 (Box 45B, Folder 13)
  - Box Office Reports - Curious Savage, 1951 (Box 45B, Folder 14)
  - Box Office Reports - Dear Me, the Sky is Falling, 1969 (Box 45B, Folder 15)
  - Box Office Reports - Devil's Disciple, 1965 (Box 45B, Folder 16)
  - Box Office Reports - Death of a Salesman, 1965 (Box 45B, Folder 17)
  - Box Office Reports - Do Your Own Thing, 1970 (Box 45B, Folder 18)
  - Box Office Reports - Dr. Doolittle, 1970 (Box 45B, Folder 19)
  - Box Office Reports - Dracula, 1970 (Box 45B, Folder 20)
  - Box Office Reports - Elves and the Shoemaker, 1954 (Box 45B, Folder 21)
  - Box Office Reports - Elves and the Shoemaker, 1973 (Box 45C, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - Emlyn Williams Presents Charles Dickens, 1971 (Box 45C, Folder 2)
  - Box Office Reports - Enter a Free Man, 1972 (Box 45C, Folder 3)
  - Box Office Reports - The Entertainer, 1966 (Box 45C, Folder 4)
  - Box Office Reports - An Evening with Arthur Miller, 1967 (Box 45C, Folder 5)
  - Box Office Reports - Everything in the Garden, 1970 (Box 45C, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Reports - The Fantasticks, 1967 (Box 45C, Folder 7)
  - Box Office Reports - Fiddler on the Roof, 1972 (Box 45C, Folder 8)
  - Box Office Reports - Films, 1972-1973 (Box 46A, Folder 1-12)
  - Box Office Reports - Films, 1970-1972 (Box 46B, Folder 1-11)
  - Box Office Reports - Films, 1969-1970 (Box 46C, Folder 1-6)
  - Box Office Reports - Films, 1957-1969 (Box 46D, Folder 1-4)
  - Box Office Reports - The Firebugs, 1965 (Box 47A, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - Flibberty Gibbet, 1955 (Box 47A, Folder 2)
  - Box Office Reports - Forest Ring, 1951 (Box 47A, Folder 3)
  - Box Office Reports - Forest Ring, 1955 (Box 47A, Folder 4)
  - Box Office Reports - Forty Carats, 1973 (Box 47A, Folder 5)
  - Box Office Reports - Frog Princess, 1970 (Box 47A, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Reports - Funny Thing Happened On the Way To The Forum, 1965 (Box 47A, Folder 7)
  - Box Office Reports - Georgy Girl, 1969 (Box 47A, Folder 8)
  - Box Office Reports - Ghost of Mr. Penny, 1950 (Box 47A, Folder 9)
  - Box Office Reports - Ghost of Mr. Penny, 1954 (Box 47A, Folder 10)
  - Box Office Reports - Ghost of Mr. Penny, 1967 (Box 47A, Folder 11)
  - Box Office Reports - Ghost Sonata, 1970 (Box 47A, Folder 12)
  - Box Office Reports - Girl on the Via Flamina, 1955 (Box 47B, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - Glass Menagerie, 1965 (Box 47B, Folder 2)
  - Box Office Reports - Goldilocks and the Three Bears, 1972 (Box 47B, Folder 3)
  - Box Office Reports - The Great Sebastian, 1965 (Box 47B, Folder 4)
  - Box Office Reports - Guys and Dolls, 1971 (Box 47B, Folder 5)
  - Box Office Reports - Gypsy, 1969 (Box 47B, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Reports - Hansel and Gretel, 1950 (Box 47B, Folder 7)
  - Box Office Reports - Hansel and Gretel, 1972 (Box 47B, Folder 8)
  - Box Office Reports - Hansel and Gretel, 1967 (Box 47B, Folder 9)
  - Box Office Reports - Happy Days Plus Two, 1969 (Box 47B, Folder 10)
  - Box Office Reports - The Happy Time, 1952 (Box 47B, Folder 11)
  - Box Office Reports - The Hasty Heart, 1947 (Box 47B, Folder 12)
  - Box Office Reports - Hay Fever, 1970 (Box 47B, Folder 13)
  - Box Office Reports - Hell's Angels "69", 1971 (Box 47B, Folder 14)
  - Box Office Reports - The Holly and the Ivy, 1953 (Box 47B, Folder 15)
  - Box Office Reports - The Hostage, 1971 (Box 47B, Folder 16)
  - Box Office Reports - How the Other Half Loves, 1972 (Box 47B, Folder 17)
  - Box Office Reports - In White America, 1965 (Box 47B, Folder 18)
  - Box Office Reports - Inspector General, 1964 (Box 47B, Folder 19)
  - Box Office Reports - Ionesco, 1969 (Box 47B, Folder 20)
  - Box Office Reports - Irma La Douce, 1970 (Box 47B, Folder 21)
  - Box Office Reports - Jack and the Beanstalk, 1971 (Box 47C, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - Joe Egg, 1970 (Box 47C, Folder 2)
  - Box Office Reports - Juno and the Paycock, 1946 (Box 47C, Folder 3)
  - Box Office Reports - King and I, 1969 (Box 47C, Folder 4)
  - Box Office Reports - King Arthur and the Magic Sword, 1967 (Box 47C, Folder 5)
  - Box Office Reports - King Lear, 1965 (Box 47C, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Reports - King Midas and the Golden Touch, 1954 (Box 47C, Folder 7)
  - Box Office Reports - The Knack, 1966 (Box 47C, Folder 8)
  - Box Office Reports - The Lady of Leley Square, 1947 (Box 47C, Folder 9)
  - Box Office Reports - Land of the Dragon, 1950 (Box 47C, Folder 10)
  - Box Office Reports - Land of the Dragon, 1971 (Box 47C, Folder 11)
  - Box Office Reports - Last of the Red Hot Lovers, 1973 (Box 47C, Folder 12)
  - Box Office Reports - Late Christopher Bean, 1955 (Box 47C, Folder 13)
  - Box Office Reports - Le Mans, 1973 (Box 47C, Folder 14)
  - Box Office Reports - Lillian Gish, 1970 (Box 47C, Folder 15)
  - Box Office Reports - Lion in Winter, 1972 (Box 47C, Folder 16)
  - Box Office Reports - Little Hut, 1955 (Box 47C, Folder 17)
  - Box Office Reports - Little Red Riding Hood, 1953 (Box 47C, Folder 18)
  - Box Office Reports - Little Red Riding Hood, 1971 (Box 47C, Folder 19)
  - Box Office Reports - The Little Wife, 1953 (Box 47C, Folder 20)
  - Box Office Reports - Loot, 1970 (Box 47C, Folder 21)
  - Box Office Reports - Lovers and Other Strangers, 1971 (Box 47C, Folder 22)
  - Box Office Reports - Luv, 1971 (Box 47C, Folder 23)